[
  {
    "question": "Which of the following anime is part of the Big Three?",
    "answer": 2,
    "option1":"Dragon Ball Z",
    "option2":"Bleach",
    "option3":"Attack on Titan",
    "option4":"Demon Slayer",
    "hint": "It's more discreet than the rest"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which of the following is the highest rated anime?",
    "answer": 1,
    "option1":"Fullmetal Alchemist: Brotherhood",
    "option2":"Attack on Titan",
    "option3":"Steins;Gate",
    "option4":"Kaguya-sama: Love is War",
    "hint": "October 3rd"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which of the following categories is targetted towards boys?",
    "answer": 3,
    "option1":"Seinen",
    "option2":"Shoujo",
    "option3":"Shounen",
    "option4":"Anime",
    "hint": "It translates to boy in japanese"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which of the following is known for memes, and has multiple parts?",
    "answer": 4,
    "option1":"One Piece",
    "option2":"One Punch Man",
    "option3":"Ghost Stories",
    "option4":"Jojo's Bizarre Adventure",
    "hint": "ZA WARUDO"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which of the following is known for it's toxic fanbase?",
    "answer": 2,
    "option1":"One Piece",
    "option2":"My Hero Academia",
    "option3":"Attack on Titan",
    "option4":"Naruto",
    "hint": "They sent the creator death threats when their favorite ship didn't happen"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which of the following has the most episodes?",
    "answer": 3,
    "option1":"Dragon Ball Z",
    "option2":"Naruto",
    "option3":"One Piece",
    "option4":"Bleach",
    "hint": "THE ________ IS REAL!"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which of the following is the most well known mecha anime?",
    "answer": 2,
    "option1":"Gundam Mobile",
    "option2":"Neon Genesis Evangelion",
    "option3":"Eighty-Six 86",
    "option4":"Accel World",
    "hint": "comas"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which of the following is an isekai",
    "answer": 2,
    "option1":"Goblin Slayer",
    "option2":"Sword Art Online",
    "option3":"One Punch Man",
    "option4":"Jojo's Bizarre Adventure",
    "hint": "Almost every isekai protagonist looks like the protagonist of this show"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which of the following is the most watched anime movie?",
    "answer": 1,
    "option1":"Demon Slayer: Mugen Train",
    "option2":"Spirited Away",
    "option3":"Jujutsu Kaisen: 0",
    "option4":"Your Name",
    "hint": "It also has an anime series"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which of the following aired in the Summer 2022 anime season?",
    "answer": 2,
    "option1":"Jujutsu Kaisen",
    "option2":"Lycoris Recoil",
    "option3":"Kaguya-sama: Love is War season 3",
    "option4":"Vinland Saga",
    "hint": "A genuinely wholesome show with girls shooting guns"
  }
]